"use strict";

const slogan = [
  [
    {
      question: "God's own State",
      option: [
        "Adamawa State",
        "Abia State",
        "Anambra State",
        "Akwa Ibom State",
      ],
      answer: "Abia State",
    },

    {
      question: "Highest peak of the nation",
      option: [
        "Gombe State",
        "Benue State",
        "Cross River State",
        "Adamawa State",
      ],
      answer: "Adamawa State",
    },

    {
      question: "Land of promise",
      option: [
        "Benue State",
        "Bauchi State",
        "Akwa Ibom State",
        "Bayelsa State",
      ],
      answer: "Akwa Ibom State",
    },

    {
      question: "Light of the nation",
      option: ["Anambra State", "Jigawa State", "Kebbi State", "Kogi State"],
      answer: "Anambra State",
    },

    {
      question: "Pearl of Tourism",
      option: ["Kwara State", "Ikeja State", "Bauchi State", "Lagos State"],
      answer: "Bauchi State",
    },

    {
      question: "The Glory of All Lands",
      option: ["Bayelsa State", "Jigawa State", "Yobe State", "Ogun State"],
      answer: "Bayelsa State",
    },

    {
      question: "Food basket of the Nation",
      option: ["Rivers State", "Taraba State", "Benue State", "Zamfara State"],
      answer: "Benue State",
    },

    {
      question: "Home of Peace",
      option: ["Borno State", "Taraba State", "Osun State", "Niger State"],
      answer: "Borno State",
    },

    {
      question: "The people's paradise",
      option: [
        "Kebbi State",
        "Enugu State",
        "Cross River State",
        "Ekiti State",
      ],
      answer: "Cross River State",
    },

    {
      question: "The Finger of God",
      option: ["Katsina State", "Delta State", "Lagos State", "Rivers State"],
      answer: "Delta State",
    },

    {
      question: "The salt of the nation",
      option: ["Ebonyi State", "Kebbi State", "Osun State", "Ekiti State"],
      answer: "Ebonyi State",
    },

    {
      question: "The Heart Beat of the Nation",
      option: ["Edo State", "Ondo State", "Borno State", "Akwa Ibom State"],
      answer: "Edo State",
    },

    {
      question: "Land of honour and integrity",
      option: ["Yobe State", "Delta State", "Oyo State", "Ekiti State"],
      answer: "Ekiti State",
    },

    {
      question: "Coal City State",
      option: ["Delta State", "Nasarawa State", "Ekiti State", "Enugu State"],
      answer: "Enugu State",
    },

    {
      question: "Jewel in the Savannah",
      option: ["Gombe State", "Benue State", "Kaduna State", "Edo State"],
      answer: "Gombe State",
    },

    {
      question: "Eastern heartland",
      option: ["Gombe State", "Kebbi State", "Imo State", "Katsina State"],
      answer: "Imo State",
    },

    {
      question: "The New World",
      option: ["Kogi State", "Borno State", "Bayelsa State", "Jigawa State"],
      answer: "Jigawa State",
    },

    {
      question: "Centre of learning",
      option: ["Bauchi State", "Lagos State", "Kaduna State", "Abia State"],
      answer: "Kaduna State",
    },

    {
      question: "Centre of Commerce",
      option: ["Abia State", "Ekiti State", "Kano State", "Anambra State"],
      answer: "Kano State",
    },

    {
      question: "State of Hospitality",
      option: ["Ekiti State", "Jigawa State", "Benue State", "Katsina State"],
      answer: "Katsina State",
    },

    {
      question: "Land of Equity",
      option: ["Plateau State", "Gombe State", "Kebbi State", "Nasarawa State"],
      answer: "Kebbi State",
    },

    {
      question: "The Confluence State",
      option: ["Lagos State", "Imo State", "Kaduna State", "Kogi State"],
      answer: "Kogi State",
    },

    {
      question: "The state of Harmony",
      option: ["Taraba State", "Kwara State", "Imo State", "Ebonyi State"],
      answer: "Kwara State",
    },

    {
      question: "Centre of Excellence",
      option: ["Imo State", "Ondo State", "Sokoto State", "Lagos State"],
      answer: "Lagos State",
    },

    {
      question: "The home of Solid Minerals",
      option: ["Rivers State", "Gombe State", "Sokoto State", "Nasarawa State"],
      answer: "Nasarawa State",
    },

    {
      question: "The power State",
      option: ["Jigawa State", "Enugu State", "Niger State", "Kogi State"],
      answer: "Niger State",
    },

    {
      question: "The Gateway State",
      option: ["Kwara State", "Osun State", "Ogun State", "Anambra State"],
      answer: "Ogun State",
    },

    {
      question: "The sunshine State",
      option: ["Delta State", "Ondo State", "Imo State", "Yobe State"],
      answer: "Ondo State",
    },

    {
      question: "Land of virtue",
      option: ["Osun State", "Bayelsa State", "Edo State", "Anambra State"],
      answer: "Osun State",
    },

    {
      question: "The pace setter State",
      option: ["Abia State", "Oyo State", "Lagos State", "Imo State"],
      answer: "Oyo State",
    },

    {
      question: "Home of peace and tourism",
      option: [
        "Zamfara State",
        "Bauchi State",
        "Adamawa State",
        "Plateau State",
      ],
      answer: "Plateau State",
    },

    {
      question: "Treasure base of the Nation",
      option: ["Delta State", "Edo State", "Enugu State", "Rivers State"],
      answer: "Rivers State",
    },

    {
      question: "Seat of the Caliphate",
      option: ["Kogi State", "Zamfara State", "Sokoto State", "Taraba State"],
      answer: "Sokoto State",
    },

    {
      question: "Nature's gift to the Nation",
      option: ["Taraba State", "Yobe State", "Lagos State", "Oyo State"],
      answer: "Taraba State",
    },

    {
      question: "Pride of the Sahel",
      option: ["Imo State", "Oyo State", "Yobe State", "Osun State"],
      answer: "Yobe State",
    },

    {
      question: "Farming is our pride",
      option: ["Plateau State", "Jigawa State", "Zamfara State", "Oyo State"],
      answer: "Zamfara State",
    },
  ],
  {
    quizTime: 105,
  },
];
